[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ae"
  },
  "question": "What type of system is NetSuite?",
  "options": [
    "CMS",
    "ERP",
    "CRM",
    "Project Management"
  ],
  "answer": "ERP",
  "category": "NetSuite"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065af"
  },
  "question": "Which company owns NetSuite?",
  "options": [
    "Microsoft",
    "Oracle",
    "Salesforce",
    "SAP"
  ],
  "answer": "Oracle",
  "category": "NetSuite"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b0"
  },
  "question": "Which feature allows users to create custom fields, records, and forms?",
  "options": [
    "Advanced Analytics",
    "Customization Center",
    "SuiteBuilder",
    "SuiteScript"
  ],
  "answer": "SuiteBuilder",
  "category": "NetSuite"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b1"
  },
  "question": "What is a Saved Search?",
  "options": [
    "A script for custom calculations",
    "A feature for saving financial reports",
    "A tool for creating reusable reports",
    "A way to save global search history"
  ],
  "answer": "A tool for creating reusable reports",
  "category": "NetSuite"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b2"
  },
  "category": "Salesforce",
  "question": "What is Salesforce primarily used for?",
  "options": [
    "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)",
    "Video Editing",
    "Web Hosting",
    "Operating System Development"
  ],
  "answer": "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b3"
  },
  "category": "Salesforce",
  "question": "Which programming language is used to customize Salesforce?",
  "options": [
    "Java",
    "Apex",
    "Python",
    "Ruby"
  ],
  "answer": "Apex"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b4"
  },
  "category": "Salesforce",
  "question": "What is a key feature of Salesforce that allows automation?",
  "options": [
    "Workflows",
    "Lightning Components",
    "AppExchange",
    "Reports"
  ],
  "answer": "Workflows"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b5"
  },
  "category": "Salesforce",
  "question": "What is the name of Salesforce's mobile app?",
  "options": [
    "Salesforce Anywhere",
    "Salesforce Connect",
    "Salesforce Mobile",
    "Salesforce One"
  ],
  "answer": "Salesforce One"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b6"
  },
  "category": "HubSpot",
  "question": "What is HubSpot primarily used for?",
  "options": [
    " Content Management",
    " Customer Relationship Management (CRM)",
    " Email Marketing",
    " Web Development"
  ],
  "answer": "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b7"
  },
  "category": "HubSpot",
  "question": "Which of the following is a tool offered by HubSpot?",
  "options": [
    " Marketing Hub",
    " Adobe Photoshop",
    " Google Analytics",
    " Slack"
  ],
  "answer": "Marketing Hub"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b8"
  },
  "category": "HubSpot",
  "question": "Which type of businesses typically use HubSpot?",
  "options": [
    " Small to Medium Businesses",
    " Large Corporations Only",
    " Freelancers and Consultants",
    " Government Agencies"
  ],
  "answer": "Small to Medium Businesses"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065b9"
  },
  "category": "HubSpot",
  "question": "What feature is a part of HubSpot's CRM platform?",
  "options": [
    " Content Creation",
    " Lead and Contact Management",
    " Video Editing",
    " Social Media Management"
  ],
  "answer": "Lead and Contact Management"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ba"
  },
  "category": "Slack",
  "question": "What is Slack primarily used for?",
  "options": [
    "File Sharing",
    "Team Communication and Collaboration",
    "Email Marketing",
    "Social Media Management"
  ],
  "answer": "Team Communication and Collaboration"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065bb"
  },
  "category": "Slack",
  "question": "Which feature does Slack offer to organize conversations?",
  "options": [
    "Channels",
    "Social Media Feeds",
    "Email Lists",
    "Newsletters"
  ],
  "answer": "Channels"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065bc"
  },
  "category": "Slack",
  "question": "What can users integrate with Slack?",
  "options": [
    "GitHub",
    "Salesforce",
    "Google Drive",
    "All of the Above"
  ],
  "answer": "All of the Above"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065bd"
  },
  "category": "Slack",
  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Slack feature?",
  "options": [
    "Direct Messaging",
    "Group Video Calls",
    "Task Management",
    "Calendar Integration"
  ],
  "answer": "Task Management"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065be"
  },
  "category": "OpenAI",
  "question": "What is OpenAI primarily focused on?",
  "options": [
    "Building robots",
    "Developing Artificial General Intelligence (AGI)",
    "Creating video games",
    "Developing virtual reality"
  ],
  "answer": "Developing Artificial General Intelligence (AGI)"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065bf"
  },
  "category": "OpenAI",
  "question": "Which of the following is a product of OpenAI?",
  "options": [
    "GPT-3",
    "Microsoft Word",
    "Google Assistant",
    "Alexa"
  ],
  "answer": "GPT-3"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c0"
  },
  "category": "OpenAI",
  "question": "What is the primary goal of OpenAI?",
  "options": [
    "To create AI for games",
    "To ensure that artificial intelligence benefits humanity",
    "To automate social media",
    "To develop AI for healthcare only"
  ],
  "answer": "To ensure that artificial intelligence benefits humanity"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c1"
  },
  "category": "OpenAI",
  "question": "Which of the following is a key feature of GPT-3?",
  "options": [
    "It generates human-like text based on prompts",
    "It is a video editing tool",
    "It is a hardware device",
    "It only processes images"
  ],
  "answer": "It generates human-like text based on prompts"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c2"
  },
  "category": "Zendesk",
  "question": "What is Zendesk best known for?",
  "options": [
    "E-commerce tools",
    "Customer Service and Support Software",
    "Content Management System",
    "Social Media Management"
  ],
  "answer": "Customer Service and Support Software"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c3"
  },
  "category": "Zendesk",
  "question": "Which of the following can you use Zendesk for?",
  "options": [
    "Handling customer support tickets",
    "Building websites",
    "Managing social media accounts",
    "Designing graphic content"
  ],
  "answer": "Handling customer support tickets"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c4"
  },
  "category": "Zendesk",
  "question": "Which feature does Zendesk provide to help with customer interactions?",
  "options": [
    "Knowledge Base",
    "File Storage",
    "Video Conferencing",
    "Marketing Automation"
  ],
  "answer": "Knowledge Base"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c5"
  },
  "category": "Zendesk",
  "question": "What type of businesses typically use Zendesk?",
  "options": [
    "E-commerce and customer support teams",
    "Video game companies",
    "Health organizations",
    "Educational institutions"
  ],
  "answer": "E-commerce and customer support teams"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c6"
  },
  "category": "Indian History",
  "question": "Who was the first emperor of the Maurya Dynasty?",
  "options": [
    "Chandragupta Maurya",
    "Ashoka the Great",
    "Bindusara",
    "Bimbisara"
  ],
  "answer": "Chandragupta Maurya"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c7"
  },
  "category": "Indian History",
  "question": "Which Indian leader is known for his role in the Non-Cooperation Movement of 1920?",
  "options": [
    "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
    "Subhas Chandra Bose"
  ],
  "answer": "Mahatma Gandhi"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c8"
  },
  "category": "Indian History",
  "question": "Who was the founder of the Mughal Empire in India?",
  "options": [
    "Akbar",
    "Babur",
    "Shah Jahan",
    "Aurangzeb"
  ],
  "answer": "Babur"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065c9"
  },
  "category": "Indian History",
  "question": "What was the name of the famous battle where Prithviraj Chauhan was defeated by Muhammad Ghori?",
  "options": [
    "Battle of Panipat",
    "Battle of Tarain",
    "Battle of Plassey",
    "Battle of Haldighati"
  ],
  "answer": "Battle of Tarain"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ca"
  },
  "category": "Indian Economy",
  "question": "Which is the largest sector of India's economy?",
  "options": [
    "Agriculture",
    "Manufacturing",
    "Services",
    "Construction"
  ],
  "answer": "Services"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065cb"
  },
  "category": "Indian Economy",
  "question": "Which of the following is the main source of income for the Government of India?",
  "options": [
    "Direct Taxes",
    "Export Revenues",
    "Foreign Aid",
    "Tourism"
  ],
  "answer": "Direct Taxes"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065cc"
  },
  "category": "Indian Economy",
  "question": "What is the official currency of India?",
  "options": [
    "Dollar",
    "Rupee",
    "Pound",
    "Yen"
  ],
  "answer": "Rupee"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065cd"
  },
  "category": "Indian Economy",
  "question": "Which institution regulates the monetary policy of India?",
  "options": [
    "Reserve Bank of India",
    "Indian Finance Ministry",
    "Securities and Exchange Board of India",
    "World Bank"
  ],
  "answer": "Reserve Bank of India"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ce"
  },
  "category": "Geography",
  "question": "What is the capital of India?",
  "options": [
    "Mumbai",
    "Kolkata",
    "New Delhi",
    "Chennai"
  ],
  "answer": "New Delhi"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065cf"
  },
  "category": "Geography",
  "question": "Which is the longest river in India?",
  "options": [
    "Ganges",
    "Godavari",
    "Yamuna",
    "Indus"
  ],
  "answer": "Ganges"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d0"
  },
  "category": "Geography",
  "question": "Which state is known as the 'Land of the Rising Sun' in India?",
  "options": [
    "Arunachal Pradesh",
    "Nagaland",
    "Sikkim",
    "Himachal Pradesh"
  ],
  "answer": "Arunachal Pradesh"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d1"
  },
  "category": "Geography",
  "question": "What is the highest peak in India?",
  "options": [
    "Kangchenjunga",
    "Mount Everest",
    "Nanda Devi",
    "Makalu"
  ],
  "answer": "Kangchenjunga"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d2"
  },
  "category": "Indian Politics",
  "question": "Who was the first Prime Minister of India?",
  "options": [
    "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "Indira Gandhi",
    "Rajiv Gandhi",
    "Lal Bahadur Shastri"
  ],
  "answer": "Jawaharlal Nehru"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d3"
  },
  "category": "Indian Politics",
  "question": "Which political party was founded by Dr. B.R. Ambedkar?",
  "options": [
    "Indian National Congress",
    "Bharatiya Janata Party",
    "Dalit Panther Party",
    "Republican Party of India"
  ],
  "answer": "Republican Party of India"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d4"
  },
  "category": "Indian Politics",
  "question": "Which article of the Indian Constitution gives the right to equality?",
  "options": [
    "Article 15",
    "Article 17",
    "Article 21",
    "Article 14"
  ],
  "answer": "Article 14"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d5"
  },
  "category": "Indian Politics",
  "question": "Who is the head of the Indian state?",
  "options": [
    "Prime Minister",
    "President",
    "Vice President",
    "Chief Justice of India"
  ],
  "answer": "President"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d6"
  },
  "category": "Budget and Taxation",
  "question": "What is the primary source of revenue for the Indian government?",
  "options": [
    "Taxes",
    "Loans from International Bodies",
    "Sale of Government Bonds",
    "Private Investments"
  ],
  "answer": "Taxes"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d7"
  },
  "category": "Budget and Taxation",
  "question": "Which tax is levied on goods and services in India?",
  "options": [
    "Goods and Services Tax (GST)",
    "Income Tax",
    "Wealth Tax",
    "Customs Duty"
  ],
  "answer": "Goods and Services Tax (GST)"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d8"
  },
  "category": "Budget and Taxation",
  "question": "Which Indian department is responsible for managing national finances?",
  "options": [
    "Ministry of Finance",
    "Reserve Bank of India",
    "Securities and Exchange Board of India",
    "Income Tax Department"
  ],
  "answer": "Ministry of Finance"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065d9"
  },
  "category": "Budget and Taxation",
  "question": "What is the fiscal year for India?",
  "options": [
    "January-December",
    "April-March",
    "June-May",
    "October-September"
  ],
  "answer": "April-March"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065da"
  },
  "category": "Space",
  "question": "Which was the first satellite launched by India?",
  "options": [
    "INSAT-1A",
    "Aryabhata",
    "Chandrayaan-1",
    "Mangalyaan"
  ],
  "answer": "Aryabhata"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065db"
  },
  "category": "Space",
  "question": "Which Indian organization is responsible for space research and satellite launches?",
  "options": [
    "ISRO",
    "NASA",
    "ESA",
    "JAXA"
  ],
  "answer": "ISRO"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065dc"
  },
  "category": "Space",
  "question": "What is the name of India's Mars Orbiter Mission?",
  "options": [
    "Mangalyaan",
    "Chandrayaan",
    "Astrosat",
    "Gaganyaan"
  ],
  "answer": "Mangalyaan"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065dd"
  },
  "category": "Space",
  "question": "Who was the first Indian to travel into space?",
  "options": [
    "Rakesh Sharma",
    "Kalpana Chawla",
    "Sunita Williams",
    "Vikram Sarabhai"
  ],
  "answer": "Rakesh Sharma"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065de"
  },
  "category": "C",
  "question": "What is the size of an int variable in C?",
  "options": [
    "1 bytes",
    "4 bytes",
    "8 bytes",
    "16 bytes"
  ],
  "answer": "4 bytes"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065df"
  },
  "category": "C",
  "question": "Which function is used to allocate memory dynamically in C?",
  "options": [
    "malloc()",
    "calloc()",
    "realloc()",
    "free()"
  ],
  "answer": "malloc()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e0"
  },
  "category": "C",
  "question": "What is the purpose of the 'break' statement in C?",
  "options": [
    "To terminate a loop",
    "To pause a loop",
    "To start a loop",
    "To call a function"
  ],
  "answer": "To terminate a loop"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e1"
  },
  "category": "C",
  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid data type in C?",
  "options": [
    "int",
    "char",
    "boolean",
    "float"
  ],
  "answer": "boolean"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e2"
  },
  "category": "C++",
  "question": "Which of the following is a feature of Object-Oriented Programming in C++?",
  "options": [
    "Encapsulation",
    "Inheritance",
    "Polymorphism",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "answer": "All of the above"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e3"
  },
  "category": "C++",
  "question": "Which of the following is used to define a class in C++?",
  "options": [
    "class ClassName {}",
    "object ClassName {}",
    "def ClassName {}",
    "struct ClassName {}"
  ],
  "answer": "class ClassName {}"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e4"
  },
  "category": "C++",
  "question": "What does the 'public' keyword represent in a C++ class?",
  "options": [
    "Private access modifier",
    "Protected access modifier",
    "Public access modifier",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "answer": "Public access modifier"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e5"
  },
  "category": "C++",
  "question": "Which operator is used to access members of a class in C++?",
  "options": [
    ".",
    "->",
    "&",
    "*"
  ],
  "answer": "."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e6"
  },
  "category": "JavaScript",
  "question": "What is the correct syntax to print a message in the console?",
  "options": [
    "print('Hello World')",
    "console.log('Hello World')",
    "echo('Hello World')",
    "printf('Hello World')"
  ],
  "answer": "console.log('Hello World')"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e7"
  },
  "category": "JavaScript",
  "question": "Which company developed JavaScript?",
  "options": [
    "Microsoft",
    "Apple",
    "Netscape",
    "Oracle"
  ],
  "answer": "Netscape"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e8"
  },
  "category": "JavaScript",
  "question": "What is the result of 2 + '2' in JavaScript?",
  "options": [
    "22",
    "4",
    "Error",
    "NaN"
  ],
  "answer": "22"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065e9"
  },
  "category": "JavaScript",
  "question": "Which method is used to add a new element at the end of an array in JavaScript?",
  "options": [
    "append()",
    "push()",
    "insert()",
    "add()"
  ],
  "answer": "push()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ea"
  },
  "category": "Java",
  "question": "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
  "options": [
    "true",
    "false",
    "null",
    "0"
  ],
  "answer": "false"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065eb"
  },
  "category": "Java",
  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a primitive data type in Java?",
  "options": [
    "int",
    "float",
    "String",
    "boolean"
  ],
  "answer": "String"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ec"
  },
  "category": "Java",
  "question": "Which method is used to start a thread in Java?",
  "options": [
    "start()",
    "run()",
    "execute()",
    "begin()"
  ],
  "answer": "start()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ed"
  },
  "category": "Java",
  "question": "What is the correct way to declare a variable in Java?",
  "options": [
    "int 1a;",
    "int a;",
    "int a = 5;",
    "int = a 5;"
  ],
  "answer": "int a = 5;"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ee"
  },
  "category": "Python",
  "question": "Which of the following is used to define a function in Python?",
  "options": [
    "def function_name():",
    "function function_name():",
    "func function_name():",
    "create function_name():"
  ],
  "answer": "def function_name():"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ef"
  },
  "category": "Python",
  "question": "What is the output of the following Python code: print(2 + 3 * 4)?",
  "options": [
    "14",
    "20",
    "26",
    "10"
  ],
  "answer": "14"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f0"
  },
  "category": "Python",
  "question": "Which method is used to remove whitespace from the beginning and end of a string in Python?",
  "options": [
    "strip()",
    "trim()",
    "cut()",
    "remove()"
  ],
  "answer": "strip()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f1"
  },
  "category": "Python",
  "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to write a list in Python?",
  "options": [
    "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
    "(1, 2, 3, 4)",
    "{1, 2, 3, 4}",
    "<1, 2, 3, 4>"
  ],
  "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f2"
  },
  "category": "React",
  "question": "What is React primarily used for?",
  "options": [
    "Building mobile apps",
    "Building user interfaces",
    "Building databases",
    "Building web servers"
  ],
  "answer": "Building user interfaces"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f3"
  },
  "category": "React",
  "question": "Which function is used to create a component in React?",
  "options": [
    "React.createElement()",
    "createComponent()",
    "function Component()",
    "React.Component()"
  ],
  "answer": "React.createElement()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f4"
  },
  "category": "React",
  "question": "What is JSX in React?",
  "options": [
    "A JavaScript syntax extension that allows HTML-like code in JavaScript",
    "A new programming language",
    "A tool for styling components",
    "A React library"
  ],
  "answer": "A JavaScript syntax extension that allows HTML-like code in JavaScript"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f5"
  },
  "category": "React",
  "question": "Which method is used to update the state in React?",
  "options": [
    "setState()",
    "updateState()",
    "changeState()",
    "setStateValue()"
  ],
  "answer": "setState()"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f6"
  },
  "category": "Algebra",
  "question": "What is the solution to the equation 2x + 3 = 11?",
  "options": [
    "x = 4",
    "x = 5",
    "x = 2",
    "x = 3"
  ],
  "answer": "x = 4"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f7"
  },
  "category": "Algebra",
  "question": "What is the value of 'x' in the equation 3x - 7 = 5x + 1?",
  "options": [
    "x = -4",
    "x = 6",
    "x = 4",
    "x = -2"
  ],
  "answer": "x = -4"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f8"
  },
  "category": "Algebra",
  "question": "Which of the following is the expanded form of (x + 2)(x - 3)?",
  "options": [
    "x^2 - x - 6",
    "x^2 - x + 6",
    "x^2 - 5x - 6",
    "x^2 - 5x + 6"
  ],
  "answer": "x^2 - 5x - 6"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065f9"
  },
  "category": "Algebra",
  "question": "What is the quadratic formula used to solve ax^2 + bx + c = 0?",
  "options": [
    "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
    "x = (-b ± √(b^2 + 4ac)) / 2a",
    "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - ac)) / a",
    "x = (-b ± √(a^2 - bc)) / 2a"
  ],
  "answer": "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - 4ac)) / 2a"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065fa"
  },
  "category": "Geometry",
  "question": "What is the area of a triangle with a base of 5 units and height of 6 units?",
  "options": [
    "15 square units",
    "10 square units",
    "12 square units",
    "30 square units"
  ],
  "answer": "15 square units"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065fb"
  },
  "category": "Geometry",
  "question": "What is the sum of the interior angles of a triangle?",
  "options": [
    "180°",
    "360°",
    "90°",
    "270°"
  ],
  "answer": "180°"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065fc"
  },
  "category": "Geometry",
  "question": "What is the volume of a cube with side length 4 units?",
  "options": [
    "16 cubic units",
    "64 cubic units",
    "48 cubic units",
    "32 cubic units"
  ],
  "answer": "64 cubic units"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065fd"
  },
  "category": "Geometry",
  "question": "What is the circumference of a circle with a radius of 7 units? (Use π = 3.14)",
  "options": [
    "21.98 units",
    "14 units",
    "49 units",
    "44.02 units"
  ],
  "answer": "43.96 units"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065fe"
  },
  "category": "Arithmetic",
  "question": "What is 25% of 200?",
  "options": [
    "50",
    "75",
    "100",
    "25"
  ],
  "answer": "50"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb97065ff"
  },
  "category": "Arithmetic",
  "question": "What is the sum of 123 + 456?",
  "options": [
    "579",
    "589",
    "599",
    "600"
  ],
  "answer": "579"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706600"
  },
  "category": "Arithmetic",
  "question": "If you subtract 15 from 50, what is the result?",
  "options": [
    "35",
    "45",
    "50",
    "25"
  ],
  "answer": "35"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706601"
  },
  "category": "Arithmetic",
  "question": "What is the product of 12 and 9?",
  "options": [
    "108",
    "100",
    "110",
    "120"
  ],
  "answer": "108"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706602"
  },
  "category": "Logical Reasoning",
  "question": "If all roses are flowers and some flowers fade quickly, can it be concluded that some roses fade quickly?",
  "options": [
    "Yes",
    "No",
    "Cannot be determined",
    "Always"
  ],
  "answer": "Cannot be determined"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706603"
  },
  "category": "Logical Reasoning",
  "question": "If two pencils are put in a box, and one pencil is taken out, how many pencils remain in the box?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "2",
    "0",
    "3"
  ],
  "answer": "1"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706604"
  },
  "category": "Logical Reasoning",
  "question": "Which of the following is the odd one out?",
  "options": [
    "Dog",
    "Lion",
    "Tiger",
    "Owl"
  ],
  "answer": "Owl"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706605"
  },
  "category": "Logical Reasoning",
  "question": "If all humans are mammals, and John is a human, is John a mammal?",
  "options": [
    "Yes",
    "No",
    "Cannot be determined",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "answer": "Yes"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706606"
  },
  "category": "Trigonometry",
  "question": "What is the sine of 30°?",
  "options": [
    "1/2",
    "√3/2",
    "√2/2",
    "1"
  ],
  "answer": "1/2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706607"
  },
  "category": "Trigonometry",
  "question": "What is the value of cos(90°)?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "0",
    "-1",
    "undefined"
  ],
  "answer": "0"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706608"
  },
  "category": "Trigonometry",
  "question": "What is the tan(45°)?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "0",
    "√3",
    "undefined"
  ],
  "answer": "1"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706609"
  },
  "category": "Trigonometry",
  "question": "What is the Pythagorean identity in trigonometry?",
  "options": [
    "sin²θ + cos²θ = 1",
    "tan²θ + sec²θ = 1",
    "sin²θ + tan²θ = 1",
    "cos²θ + sec²θ = 1"
  ],
  "answer": "sin²θ + cos²θ = 1"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660a"
  },
  "category": "Cricket",
  "question": "Who holds the record for the most runs in a single ODI match?",
  "options": [
    "Sachin Tendulkar",
    "Rohit Sharma",
    "Virat Kohli",
    "Ricky Ponting"
  ],
  "answer": "Rohit Sharma"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660b"
  },
  "category": "Cricket",
  "question": "What is the maximum number of overs in a standard One Day International (ODI) match?",
  "options": [
    "10",
    "20",
    "30",
    "50"
  ],
  "answer": "50"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660c"
  },
  "category": "Cricket",
  "question": "Who is the captain of the Indian national cricket team in limited-overs formats (ODI and TEST)?",
  "options": [
    "Virat Kohli",
    "MS Dhoni",
    "Rohit Sharma",
    "Sourav Ganguly"
  ],
  "answer": "Rohit Sharma"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660d"
  },
  "category": "Cricket",
  "question": "What is the highest individual score in a T20I match?",
  "options": [
    "122",
    "118",
    "156",
    "175"
  ],
  "answer": "175"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660e"
  },
  "category": "Football",
  "question": "Which country won the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
  "options": [
    "Brazil",
    "Germany",
    "France",
    "Argentina"
  ],
  "answer": "France"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970660f"
  },
  "category": "Football",
  "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Football'?",
  "options": [
    "Lionel Messi",
    "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "Pele",
    "Diego Maradona"
  ],
  "answer": "Pele"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706610"
  },
  "category": "Football",
  "question": "Which club does Cristiano Ronaldo currently play for (as of 2024)?",
  "options": [
    "Real Madrid",
    "Manchester United",
    "Juventus",
    "Al Nassr"
  ],
  "answer": "Al Nassr"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706611"
  },
  "category": "Football",
  "question": "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
  "options": [
    "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "Lionel Messi",
    "Michel Platini",
    "Zinedine Zidane"
  ],
  "answer": "Lionel Messi"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706612"
  },
  "category": "Hockey",
  "question": "Which country won the 2020 Men's Field Hockey Olympic Gold Medal?",
  "options": [
    "India",
    "Germany",
    "Australia",
    "Belgium"
  ],
  "answer": "Belgium"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706613"
  },
  "category": "Hockey",
  "question": "Who is known as the 'Wizard of Hockey'?",
  "options": [
    "Dhyan Chand",
    "Sardar Singh",
    "Balbir Singh",
    "Manpreet Singh"
  ],
  "answer": "Dhyan Chand"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706614"
  },
  "category": "Hockey",
  "question": "How many players are on the field for each team in a standard hockey match?",
  "options": [
    "8",
    "10",
    "11",
    "7"
  ],
  "answer": "11"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706615"
  },
  "category": "Hockey",
  "question": "Which country is considered the birthplace of ice hockey?",
  "options": [
    "Canada",
    "USA",
    "Russia",
    "Sweden"
  ],
  "answer": "Canada"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706616"
  },
  "category": "Volleyball",
  "question": "How many players are on a team in a standard volleyball match?",
  "options": [
    "4",
    "6",
    "7",
    "5"
  ],
  "answer": "6"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706617"
  },
  "category": "Volleyball",
  "question": "What is the maximum number of hits allowed for a team before the ball must be sent over the net?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ],
  "answer": "3"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706618"
  },
  "category": "Volleyball",
  "question": "Which country won the 2020 Olympic Gold Medal in Men's Volleyball?",
  "options": [
    "Brazil",
    "USA",
    "Russia",
    "France"
  ],
  "answer": "France"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706619"
  },
  "category": "Volleyball",
  "question": "What is the term for the move where a player jumps to block the opponent's attack?",
  "options": [
    "Dig",
    "Spike",
    "Block",
    "Serve"
  ],
  "answer": "Block"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661a"
  },
  "category": "Basketball",
  "question": "Which player holds the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game?",
  "options": [
    "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "Michael Jordan",
    "LeBron James",
    "Wilt Chamberlain"
  ],
  "answer": "Wilt Chamberlain"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661b"
  },
  "category": "Basketball",
  "question": "Which NBA team has won the most championships?",
  "options": [
    "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "Boston Celtics",
    "Chicago Bulls",
    "Golden State Warriors"
  ],
  "answer": "Boston Celtics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661c"
  },
  "category": "Basketball",
  "question": "Who is known as 'The King' of basketball?",
  "options": [
    "Michael Jordan",
    "Kobe Bryant",
    "LeBron James",
    "Shaquille O'Neal"
  ],
  "answer": "LeBron James"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661d"
  },
  "category": "Basketball",
  "question": "What is the maximum number of points a player can score in a single possession (without fouls)?",
  "options": [
    "2",
    "3",
    "4",
    "5"
  ],
  "answer": "3"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661e"
  },
  "category": "Tennis",
  "question": "Which tennis player has won the most Grand Slam singles titles?",
  "options": [
    "Roger Federer",
    "Rafael Nadal",
    "Novak Djokovic",
    "Pete Sampras"
  ],
  "answer": "Rafael Nadal"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970661f"
  },
  "category": "Tennis",
  "question": "Which country is the birthplace of tennis?",
  "options": [
    "USA",
    "England",
    "France",
    "Australia"
  ],
  "answer": "England"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706620"
  },
  "category": "Tennis",
  "question": "Who won the Wimbledon men's singles title in 2023?",
  "options": [
    "Roger Federer",
    "Novak Djokovic",
    "Rafael Nadal",
    "Carlos Alcaraz"
  ],
  "answer": "Novak Djokovic"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706621"
  },
  "category": "Tennis",
  "question": "What is the term for scoring zero points in tennis?",
  "options": [
    "Love",
    "Fault",
    "Ace",
    "Deuce"
  ],
  "answer": "Love"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706622"
  },
  "category": "Action",
  "question": "Which Indian movie features the character 'Kabir' played by Hrithik Roshan?",
  "options": [
    "War",
    "Bang Bang!",
    "Dhoom 3",
    "Krrish 3"
  ],
  "answer": "War"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706623"
  },
  "category": "Action",
  "question": "In which movie did Akshay Kumar play the role of a police officer named Veer Sooryavanshi?",
  "options": [
    "Sooryavanshi",
    "Khatta Meetha",
    "Hera Pheri",
    "Khiladi 786"
  ],
  "answer": "Sooryavanshi"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706624"
  },
  "category": "Action",
  "question": "Which action movie is based on the battle between two brothers in a fictional kingdom, starring Salman Khan?",
  "options": [
    "Bajrangi Bhaijaan",
    "Kick",
    "Radhe",
    "Tubelight"
  ],
  "answer": "Radhe"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706625"
  },
  "category": "Action",
  "question": "Which film features a revenge saga starring Amitabh Bachchan as a character named Vijay?",
  "options": [
    "Zanjeer",
    "Sholay",
    "Don",
    "Agneepath"
  ],
  "answer": "Agneepath"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706626"
  },
  "category": "Comedy",
  "question": "Which film is known for the iconic character 'Chupke Chupke' starring Dharmendra, Sharmila Tagore, and Amitabh Bachchan?",
  "options": [
    "Chupke Chupke",
    "Hera Pheri",
    "Andaz Apna Apna",
    "Bheja Fry"
  ],
  "answer": "Chupke Chupke"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706627"
  },
  "category": "Comedy",
  "question": "In which comedy film does Akshay Kumar play the role of a man trying to find a woman for his sister's marriage?",
  "options": [
    "Dhadkan",
    "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi",
    "Phir Hera Pheri",
    "Housefull"
  ],
  "answer": "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706628"
  },
  "category": "Comedy",
  "question": "Which movie features a comedy duo named Amar and Prem played by Salman Khan and Akshay Kumar?",
  "options": [
    "Baaghi",
    "Andaz Apna Apna",
    "Partner",
    "No Entry"
  ],
  "answer": "Andaz Apna Apna"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706629"
  },
  "category": "Comedy",
  "question": "In which film does Rajpal Yadav play a hilarious character named 'Lallan'?",
  "options": [
    "Masti",
    "Bhool Bhulaiyaa",
    "Hera Pheri",
    "Khatta Meetha"
  ],
  "answer": "Masti"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662a"
  },
  "category": "Drama",
  "question": "Which movie stars Shah Rukh Khan as a man who befriends a woman with cancer in 'Kal Ho Naa Ho'?",
  "options": [
    "Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna",
    "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "Kal Ho Naa Ho",
    "Om Shanti Om"
  ],
  "answer": "Kal Ho Naa Ho"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662b"
  },
  "category": "Drama",
  "question": "Which drama movie is based on the life of a farmer, played by Amitabh Bachchan, fighting for justice?",
  "options": [
    "Satyagraha",
    "Sholay",
    "Paa",
    "Baghban"
  ],
  "answer": "Baghban"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662c"
  },
  "category": "Drama",
  "question": "Which film features Aamir Khan as an underdog wrestler in the movie 'Dangal'?",
  "options": [
    "3 Idiots",
    "PK",
    "Dangal",
    "Lagaan"
  ],
  "answer": "Dangal"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662d"
  },
  "category": "Drama",
  "question": "Which movie features Kajol as a woman who goes to great lengths to fulfill her late husband's wish in 'Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham'?",
  "options": [
    "Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna",
    "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
    "Pardes"
  ],
  "answer": "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662e"
  },
  "category": "Horror",
  "question": "Which movie features a supernatural story where a spirit haunts a family, starring Rajkummar Rao?",
  "options": [
    "Stree",
    "Bhoot",
    "Raaz",
    "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"
  ],
  "answer": "Stree"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970662f"
  },
  "category": "Horror",
  "question": "Which movie is based on a haunted house, featuring the character of 'Aarti' played by Rani Mukerji?",
  "options": [
    "Bhootnath",
    "Raaz",
    "Mahal",
    "Aatma"
  ],
  "answer": "Raaz"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706630"
  },
  "category": "Horror",
  "question": "In which film does Emraan Hashmi play the lead role in a thriller about paranormal activities?",
  "options": [
    "Raaz: The Mystery Continues",
    "Haunted 3D",
    "Bhoot",
    "Aatma"
  ],
  "answer": "Raaz: The Mystery Continues"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706631"
  },
  "category": "Horror",
  "question": "Which horror-comedy movie has the iconic song 'Aayi Teri Yaad'?",
  "options": [
    "Murder",
    "Bhootnath",
    "Bhool Bhulaiyaa",
    "Haunted 3D"
  ],
  "answer": "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706632"
  },
  "category": "Romance",
  "question": "In which film does Shah Rukh Khan play a character who falls in love with a woman in Switzerland?",
  "options": [
    "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
    "Dil Se",
    "Jab Tak Hai Jaan"
  ],
  "answer": "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706633"
  },
  "category": "Romance",
  "question": "Which movie features Aamir Khan and Kajol in the lead roles, where they fall in love despite their differences?",
  "options": [
    "Tujhe Meri Kasam",
    "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "Fanaa",
    "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam"
  ],
  "answer": "Fanaa"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706634"
  },
  "category": "Romance",
  "question": "Which romantic movie features Deepika Padukone and Ranbir Kapoor in the lead roles?",
  "options": [
    "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani",
    "Ae Dil Hai Mushkil",
    "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
    "Barfi!"
  ],
  "answer": "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706635"
  },
  "category": "Romance",
  "question": "Which movie revolves around a love story between a student and a teacher played by Hrithik Roshan and Aishwarya Rai?",
  "options": [
    "Jodhaa Akbar",
    "Taal",
    "Guzaarish",
    "Mohenjo Daro"
  ],
  "answer": "Guzaarish"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706636"
  },
  "category": "Thriller",
  "question": "In which movie does Hrithik Roshan play a mastermind criminal in a thrilling heist?",
  "options": [
    "Dhoom 2",
    "Bang Bang!",
    "War",
    "Krrish"
  ],
  "answer": "Dhoom 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706637"
  },
  "category": "Thriller",
  "question": "Which film features a psychological thriller about a woman who is trapped in her own home?",
  "options": [
    "Kahaani",
    "Talaash",
    "Drishyam",
    "The Shining"
  ],
  "answer": "Kahaani"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706638"
  },
  "category": "Thriller",
  "question": "In which movie does Salman Khan play a character in pursuit of a serial killer?",
  "options": [
    "Race 3",
    "Wanted",
    "Bajrangi Bhaijaan",
    "Dabangg"
  ],
  "answer": "Race 3"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706639"
  },
  "category": "Thriller",
  "question": "Which movie involves a young man who seeks revenge after being framed for a crime he did not commit?",
  "options": [
    "Drishyam",
    "Talaash",
    "Sultan",
    "Murder 2"
  ],
  "answer": "Drishyam"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663a"
  },
  "question": "Which fuel type is commonly used in cars?",
  "options": [
    "Diesel",
    "Electricity",
    "Gasoline",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "answer": "All of the above",
  "category": "Cars"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663b"
  },
  "question": "What is the typical seating capacity of a sedan car?",
  "options": [
    "2",
    "4-5",
    "6-8",
    "10+"
  ],
  "answer": "4-5",
  "category": "Cars"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663c"
  },
  "question": "Which of these features is commonly found in modern cars?",
  "options": [
    "Autonomous Driving",
    "Solar Panels",
    "Horse Saddle",
    "Steam Engine"
  ],
  "answer": "Autonomous Driving",
  "category": "Cars"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663d"
  },
  "question": "Which country is known for producing luxury cars like BMW and Mercedes-Benz?",
  "options": [
    "Japan",
    "USA",
    "Germany",
    "Italy"
  ],
  "answer": "Germany",
  "category": "Cars"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663e"
  },
  "question": "What is the primary purpose of trucks?",
  "options": [
    "Carrying passengers",
    "Transporting goods",
    "Racing",
    "Towing boats"
  ],
  "answer": "Transporting goods",
  "category": "Trucks"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970663f"
  },
  "question": "What is the term for a truck with a detachable trailer?",
  "options": [
    "Flatbed Truck",
    "Semi-Truck",
    "Dump Truck",
    "Box Truck"
  ],
  "answer": "Semi-Truck",
  "category": "Trucks"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706640"
  },
  "question": "Which type of truck is used in construction for moving materials like sand and gravel?",
  "options": [
    "Dump Truck",
    "Box Truck",
    "Tow Truck",
    "Ice Cream Truck"
  ],
  "answer": "Dump Truck",
  "category": "Trucks"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706641"
  },
  "question": "Which fuel is most commonly used in large trucks?",
  "options": [
    "Gasoline",
    "Electricity",
    "Diesel",
    "Hydrogen"
  ],
  "answer": "Diesel",
  "category": "Trucks"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706642"
  },
  "question": "Which type of train runs on electricity?",
  "options": [
    "Steam Train",
    "Diesel Train",
    "Electric Train",
    "Maglev Train"
  ],
  "answer": "Electric Train",
  "category": "Trains"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706643"
  },
  "question": "What is the term for a high-speed train that uses magnetic levitation?",
  "options": [
    "Bullet Train",
    "Maglev Train",
    "Freight Train",
    "Subway Train"
  ],
  "answer": "Maglev Train",
  "category": "Trains"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706644"
  },
  "question": "Which type of train is used for carrying goods?",
  "options": [
    "Passenger Train",
    "Freight Train",
    "Bullet Train",
    "Commuter Train"
  ],
  "answer": "Freight Train",
  "category": "Trains"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706645"
  },
  "question": "What do trains typically run on?",
  "options": [
    "Rubber Tires",
    "Tracks",
    "Dirt Roads",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "answer": "Tracks",
  "category": "Trains"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706646"
  },
  "question": "What powers a bicycle?",
  "options": [
    "Electric Motor",
    "Gasoline",
    "Human Effort",
    "Solar Energy"
  ],
  "answer": "Human Effort",
  "category": "Bicycles"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706647"
  },
  "question": "What is the primary safety gear for a cyclist?",
  "options": [
    "Helmet",
    "Gloves",
    "Knee Pads",
    "Sunglasses"
  ],
  "answer": "Helmet",
  "category": "Bicycles"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706648"
  },
  "question": "Which type of bicycle is designed for off-road cycling?",
  "options": [
    "Road Bike",
    "Mountain Bike",
    "Hybrid Bike",
    "BMX Bike"
  ],
  "answer": "Mountain Bike",
  "category": "Bicycles"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706649"
  },
  "question": "What is the common number of wheels on a standard bicycle?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ],
  "answer": "2",
  "category": "Bicycles"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664a"
  },
  "question": "Which type of ship is used for carrying goods across oceans?",
  "options": [
    "Cargo Ship",
    "Fishing Boat",
    "Speedboat",
    "Yacht"
  ],
  "answer": "Cargo Ship",
  "category": "Ships and Boats"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664b"
  },
  "question": "Which of these is a small boat used for recreation?",
  "options": [
    "Yacht",
    "Canoe",
    "Cruise Ship",
    "Submarine"
  ],
  "answer": "Canoe",
  "category": "Ships and Boats"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664c"
  },
  "question": "Which type of ship is used for passenger travel across oceans?",
  "options": [
    "Cargo Ship",
    "Fishing Boat",
    "Cruise Ship",
    "Tugboat"
  ],
  "answer": "Cruise Ship",
  "category": "Ships and Boats"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664d"
  },
  "question": "What is the primary purpose of a fishing boat?",
  "options": [
    "Transporting goods",
    "Recreation",
    "Catching fish",
    "Military defense"
  ],
  "answer": "Catching fish",
  "category": "Ships and Boats"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664e"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is a prominent Indian classical instrument used in both Hindustani and Carnatic music?",
  "options": [
    "Sitar",
    "Tabla",
    "Veena",
    "Flute"
  ],
  "answer": "Tabla",
  "category": "Indian Classical Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970664f"
  },
  "question": "What are the two major traditions of Indian classical music?",
  "options": [
    "Hindustani and Carnatic",
    "Hindustani and Western",
    "Carnatic and Folk",
    "Folk and Classical"
  ],
  "answer": "Hindustani and Carnatic",
  "category": "Indian Classical Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706650"
  },
  "question": "Who is regarded as the 'Father of Indian Classical Music'?",
  "options": [
    "Tansen",
    "Bhimsen Joshi",
    "Ravi Shankar",
    "Ustad Zakir Hussain"
  ],
  "answer": "Tansen",
  "category": "Classical Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706651"
  },
  "question": "Which raga is traditionally performed during the morning hours in Indian classical music?",
  "options": [
    "Raga Yaman",
    "Raga Bhairav",
    "Raga Hamsadhwani",
    "Raga Bhairavi"
  ],
  "answer": "Raga Bhairav",
  "category": "Classical Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706652"
  },
  "question": "Which folk music form is famous in the state of Punjab and is characterized by energetic dance movements?",
  "options": [
    "Garba",
    "Bhangra",
    "Lavani",
    "Ghoomar"
  ],
  "answer": "Bhangra",
  "category": "Folk Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706653"
  },
  "question": "Which musical instrument is commonly associated with Indian folk music, especially in Rajasthan?",
  "options": [
    "Sitar",
    "Dholak",
    "Sarangi",
    "Tanpura"
  ],
  "answer": "Sarangi",
  "category": "Indian Folk Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706654"
  },
  "question": "Which Indian state is known for its traditional folk dance form 'Garba', often performed during the Navratri festival?",
  "options": [
    "Maharashtra",
    "Gujarat",
    "Punjab",
    "Karnataka"
  ],
  "answer": "Gujarat",
  "category": "Folk Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706655"
  },
  "question": "Which folk music genre, originating from Tamil Nadu, is known for its devotional songs and was popularized by singers like T.M. Soundararajan?",
  "options": [
    "Baul",
    "Kaili",
    "Carnatic",
    "Gana"
  ],
  "answer": "Carnatic",
  "category": "Indian Folk Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706656"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered one of the pioneers of Indian rap music, known for his hit song 'Meri Indian Rap'?",
  "options": [
    "Divine",
    "Yo Yo Honey Singh",
    "Brodha V",
    "Bohemia"
  ],
  "answer": "Bohemia",
  "category": "Rap"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706657"
  },
  "question": "Which Indian rapper is famous for his breakthrough song 'Meri Gully Mein'?",
  "options": [
    "Emiway Bantai",
    "Divine",
    "Badshah",
    "Raftaar"
  ],
  "answer": "Divine",
  "category": "Rap"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706658"
  },
  "question": "Which Indian rapper's debut album 'Desi Hip-Hop' gained massive popularity in the hip-hop scene?",
  "options": [
    "Yo Yo Honey Singh",
    "Brodha V",
    "Raftaar",
    "Bohemia"
  ],
  "answer": "Yo Yo Honey Singh",
  "category": "Rap"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706659"
  },
  "question": "Which city is considered the birthplace of Indian rap, particularly known for the rise of artists like Divine and Naezy?",
  "options": [
    "Delhi",
    "Mumbai",
    "Kolkata",
    "Bangalore"
  ],
  "answer": "Mumbai",
  "category": "Rap"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665a"
  },
  "question": "Which Sufi singer is famously known for popularizing the qawwali genre with songs like 'Tajdar-e-Haram'?",
  "options": [
    "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan",
    "Abida Parveen",
    "Rahat Fateh Ali Khan",
    "Mehdi Hassan"
  ],
  "answer": "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan",
  "category": "Sufi Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665b"
  },
  "question": "What is the primary theme of Sufi music?",
  "options": [
    "Love and devotion",
    "Revolutionary ideas",
    "Romanticism",
    "Nature's beauty"
  ],
  "answer": "Love and devotion",
  "category": "Sufi Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665c"
  },
  "question": "Which form of Sufi music is a devotional genre performed in a group setting, featuring energetic chanting and rhythmic clapping?",
  "options": [
    "Qawwali",
    "Ghazal",
    "Kaili",
    "Dastan"
  ],
  "answer": "Qawwali",
  "category": "Sufi Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665d"
  },
  "question": "Which poet and philosopher, considered one of the greatest Sufi saints, is known for his works in Persian and his spiritual teachings?",
  "options": [
    "Rumi",
    "Shams Tabrizi",
    "Iqbal",
    "Khwaja Moinuddin Chishti"
  ],
  "answer": "Rumi",
  "category": "Sufi Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665e"
  },
  "question": "Which string instrument is often associated with Indian classical music and features a resonating gourd?",
  "options": [
    "Sitar",
    "Violin",
    "Guitar",
    "Veena"
  ],
  "answer": "Sitar",
  "category": "Instrumental Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970665f"
  },
  "question": "Which instrument, commonly used in orchestras, produces sound by pressing keys to allow air to flow through its pipes?",
  "options": [
    "Organ",
    "Flute",
    "Oboe",
    "Clarinet"
  ],
  "answer": "Organ",
  "category": "Instrumental Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706660"
  },
  "question": "Which percussion instrument consists of tuned metal bars arranged like a keyboard and is played with mallets?",
  "options": [
    "Marimba",
    "Xylophone",
    "Glockenspiel",
    "Vibraphone"
  ],
  "answer": "Glockenspiel",
  "category": "Instrumental Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706661"
  },
  "question": "Which instrument, known for its deep and resonant sound, is the largest member of the brass family?",
  "options": [
    "Tuba",
    "Trombone",
    "French Horn",
    "Euphonium"
  ],
  "answer": "Tuba",
  "category": "Instrumental Music"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706662"
  },
  "question": "Which political system is characterized by a single party controlling the government, and no opposition parties are allowed?",
  "options": [
    "Democracy",
    "Oligarchy",
    "Communism",
    "Dictatorship"
  ],
  "answer": "Communism",
  "category": "Political Systems"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706663"
  },
  "question": "In a parliamentary democracy, who is typically the head of government?",
  "options": [
    "President",
    "Prime Minister",
    "King",
    "Chancellor"
  ],
  "answer": "Prime Minister",
  "category": "Political Systems"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706664"
  },
  "question": "Which system of government divides power between a central government and regional governments?",
  "options": [
    "Federalism",
    "Unitary System",
    "Confederation",
    "Absolute Monarchy"
  ],
  "answer": "Federalism",
  "category": "Political Systems"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706665"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following countries has a system of government where the monarch's powers are limited by a constitution?",
  "options": [
    "United Kingdom",
    "Saudi Arabia",
    "North Korea",
    "China"
  ],
  "answer": "United Kingdom",
  "category": "Political Systems"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706666"
  },
  "question": "Who is the current Prime Minister of India?",
  "options": [
    "Narendra Modi",
    "Rahul Gandhi",
    "Manmohan Singh",
    "Atal Bihari Vajpayee"
  ],
  "answer": "Narendra Modi",
  "category": "Indian Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706667"
  },
  "question": "Which article of the Indian Constitution deals with the Fundamental Rights?",
  "options": [
    "Article 21",
    "Article 370",
    "Article 19",
    "Article 14"
  ],
  "answer": "Article 21",
  "category": "Indian Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706668"
  },
  "question": "Which political party was founded by Dr. B.R. Ambedkar and is known for advocating the rights of Dalits?",
  "options": [
    "Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP)",
    "Indian National Congress (INC)",
    "Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP)",
    "Communist Party of India (CPI)"
  ],
  "answer": "Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP)",
  "category": "Indian Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706669"
  },
  "question": "In which year did India gain independence from British rule?",
  "options": [
    "1942",
    "1947",
    "1950",
    "1960"
  ],
  "answer": "1947",
  "category": "Indian Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666a"
  },
  "question": "Which country is known for having the longest continuous democracy?",
  "options": [
    "United States",
    "United Kingdom",
    "India",
    "Switzerland"
  ],
  "answer": "United Kingdom",
  "category": "World Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666b"
  },
  "question": "Who was the first female Chancellor of Germany?",
  "options": [
    "Margaret Thatcher",
    "Angela Merkel",
    "Golda Meir",
    "Jacinda Ardern"
  ],
  "answer": "Angela Merkel",
  "category": "World Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666c"
  },
  "question": "Which international organization was established to promote peace and cooperation after World War II?",
  "options": [
    "United Nations",
    "World Trade Organization",
    "European Union",
    "International Monetary Fund"
  ],
  "answer": "United Nations",
  "category": "World Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666d"
  },
  "question": "Which country became independent from the Soviet Union in 1991 and has since become a major player in global politics?",
  "options": [
    "Ukraine",
    "Georgia",
    "Estonia",
    "Russia"
  ],
  "answer": "Russia",
  "category": "World Politics"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666e"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered the Supreme God in Hindu mythology, often depicted as the creator, preserver, and destroyer of the universe?",
  "options": [
    "Brahma",
    "Vishnu",
    "Shiva",
    "Indra"
  ],
  "answer": "Vishnu",
  "category": "Indian mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970666f"
  },
  "question": "Which demon king was defeated by Lord Rama in the epic Ramayana?",
  "options": [
    "Ravana",
    "Kumbhakarna",
    "Vibhishana",
    "Hiranyakashipu"
  ],
  "answer": "Ravana",
  "category": "Indian mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706670"
  },
  "question": "In the Mahabharata, who is the mother of the Pandavas?",
  "options": [
    "Kunti",
    "Draupadi",
    "Satyavati",
    "Gandhari"
  ],
  "answer": "Kunti",
  "category": "Indian mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706671"
  },
  "question": "Which goddess is often depicted riding a tiger or lion and is associated with strength, war, and protection?",
  "options": [
    "Saraswati",
    "Lakshmi",
    "Durga",
    "Parvati"
  ],
  "answer": "Durga",
  "category": "Indian mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706672"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered the king of the Greek gods and the ruler of Mount Olympus?",
  "options": [
    "Apollo",
    "Zeus",
    "Poseidon",
    "Hades"
  ],
  "answer": "Zeus",
  "category": "Greek Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706673"
  },
  "question": "Which Greek hero is known for his twelve labors, including slaying the Nemean Lion?",
  "options": [
    "Perseus",
    "Theseus",
    "Heracles",
    "Achilles"
  ],
  "answer": "Heracles",
  "category": "Greek Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706674"
  },
  "question": "Who is the Greek goddess of wisdom, courage, and warfare?",
  "options": [
    "Hera",
    "Athena",
    "Artemis",
    "Aphrodite"
  ],
  "answer": "Athena",
  "category": "Greek Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706675"
  },
  "question": "Which Greek god is the ruler of the underworld?",
  "options": [
    "Zeus",
    "Apollo",
    "Hades",
    "Hermes"
  ],
  "answer": "Hades",
  "category": "Greek Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706676"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered the king of the gods and ruler of the sky in Egyptian mythology?",
  "options": [
    "Ra",
    "Osiris",
    "Horus",
    "Amun"
  ],
  "answer": "Ra",
  "category": "Egyptian Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706677"
  },
  "question": "Which goddess is known as the protector of the dead and the wife of Osiris?",
  "options": [
    "Isis",
    "Nephthys",
    "Bastet",
    "Sekhmet"
  ],
  "answer": "Isis",
  "category": "Egyptian Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706678"
  },
  "question": "Who is the Egyptian god of the underworld and judge of the dead?",
  "options": [
    "Horus",
    "Anubis",
    "Thoth",
    "Osiris"
  ],
  "answer": "Osiris",
  "category": "Egyptian Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706679"
  },
  "question": "Which goddess, depicted as a lioness, is associated with war and healing?",
  "options": [
    "Sekhmet",
    "Bastet",
    "Hathor",
    "Tefnut"
  ],
  "answer": "Sekhmet",
  "category": "Egyptian Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667a"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered the king of the Roman gods and ruler of the sky?",
  "options": [
    "Jupiter",
    "Neptune",
    "Mars",
    "Apollo"
  ],
  "answer": "Jupiter",
  "category": "Roman Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667b"
  },
  "question": "Which Roman goddess is associated with love, beauty, and fertility?",
  "options": [
    "Venus",
    "Minerva",
    "Diana",
    "Ceres"
  ],
  "answer": "Venus",
  "category": "Roman Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667c"
  },
  "question": "Who is the Roman god of war, often depicted as a warrior in battle armor?",
  "options": [
    "Mars",
    "Juno",
    "Vulcan",
    "Saturn"
  ],
  "answer": "Mars",
  "category": "Roman Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667d"
  },
  "question": "Which Roman god is known as the messenger of the gods and the god of commerce and travel?",
  "options": [
    "Mercury",
    "Apollo",
    "Bacchus",
    "Pluto"
  ],
  "answer": "Mercury",
  "category": "Roman Mythology"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667e"
  },
  "question": "Which Free Fire character is known for her healing ability and is often referred to as the 'angel of battle'?",
  "options": [
    "A124",
    "Shirou",
    "Moco",
    "Paloma"
  ],
  "answer": "A124",
  "category": "Free Fire"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970667f"
  },
  "question": "Which weapon in Free Fire is famous for its long-range sniper abilities?",
  "options": [
    "AK47",
    "AWM",
    "M4A1",
    "MP40"
  ],
  "answer": "AWM",
  "category": "Free Fire"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706680"
  },
  "question": "What is the maximum number of players in a Free Fire squad?",
  "options": [
    "2",
    "3",
    "4",
    "5"
  ],
  "answer": "4",
  "category": "Free Fire"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706681"
  },
  "question": "Which Free Fire character has the ability to increase the speed of throwing grenades?",
  "options": [
    "Wukong",
    "Dasha",
    "Hayato",
    "Skyler"
  ],
  "answer": "Dasha",
  "category": "Free Fire"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706682"
  },
  "question": "Which BGMI vehicle is known for its speed and ability to cross rough terrains?",
  "options": [
    "Dacia",
    "Buggy",
    "UAZ",
    "Motorcycle"
  ],
  "answer": "Buggy",
  "category": "BGMI"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706683"
  },
  "question": "Which BGMI weapon is the most powerful sniper rifle with the highest damage?",
  "options": [
    "M416",
    "AWM",
    "Kar98k",
    "SKS"
  ],
  "answer": "AWM",
  "category": "BGMI"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706684"
  },
  "question": "What is the maximum number of players in a BGMI squad?",
  "options": [
    "2",
    "3",
    "4",
    "5"
  ],
  "answer": "4",
  "category": "BGMI"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706685"
  },
  "question": "In BGMI, which item is used to heal players over time?",
  "options": [
    "First Aid Kit",
    "Bandage",
    "Med Kit",
    "Painkiller"
  ],
  "answer": "Painkiller",
  "category": "BGMI"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706686"
  },
  "question": "Which COD game introduced the popular Zombies mode?",
  "options": [
    "Call of Duty: Modern Warfare",
    "Call of Duty: Black Ops",
    "Call of Duty: Advanced Warfare",
    "Call of Duty: World at War"
  ],
  "answer": "Call of Duty: World at War",
  "category": "COD"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706687"
  },
  "question": "Which COD weapon is known for its high damage and rate of fire, and is a favorite in multiplayer modes?",
  "options": [
    "AK-47",
    "M4A1",
    "MP5",
    "RPD"
  ],
  "answer": "MP5",
  "category": "COD"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706688"
  },
  "question": "In Call of Duty: Warzone, what is the maximum number of players in a single battle royale match?",
  "options": [
    "50",
    "100",
    "150",
    "200"
  ],
  "answer": "150",
  "category": "COD"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706689"
  },
  "question": "Which COD character is famous for saying 'The price is right' in the campaign mode?",
  "options": [
    "Soap MacTavish",
    "Captain Price",
    "Alex Mason",
    "Ghost"
  ],
  "answer": "Captain Price",
  "category": "COD"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668a"
  },
  "question": "Which city is the setting for the original Grand Theft Auto (GTA) game?",
  "options": [
    "Vice City",
    "Liberty City",
    "San Andreas",
    "London"
  ],
  "answer": "Liberty City",
  "category": "GTA"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668b"
  },
  "question": "In which GTA game did the character 'CJ' (Carl Johnson) appear?",
  "options": [
    "GTA IV",
    "GTA V",
    "GTA San Andreas",
    "GTA Vice City"
  ],
  "answer": "GTA San Andreas",
  "category": "GTA"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668c"
  },
  "question": "Which vehicle is commonly associated with the GTA series and is known for its muscle car appearance?",
  "options": [
    "Comet",
    "Banshee",
    "Infernus",
    "Sultan"
  ],
  "answer": "Infernus",
  "category": "GTA"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668d"
  },
  "question": "In Grand Theft Auto V, which of the following is NOT one of the three playable characters?",
  "options": [
    "Michael De Santa",
    "Trevor Philips",
    "Franklin Clinton",
    "Tommy Vercetti"
  ],
  "answer": "Tommy Vercetti",
  "category": "GTA"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668e"
  },
  "question": "What does IPO stand for in the context of finance?",
  "options": [
    "International Public Offering",
    "Initial Public Offering",
    "Initial Private Offering",
    "Investor's Public Offering"
  ],
  "answer": "Initial Public Offering",
  "category": "IPO"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970668f"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is a reason a company might choose to go public with an IPO?",
  "options": [
    "To raise capital for expansion",
    "To increase control over the company",
    "To avoid paying taxes",
    "To keep the company private"
  ],
  "answer": "To raise capital for expansion",
  "category": "IPO"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706690"
  },
  "question": "What is the primary purpose of an underwriter in an IPO?",
  "options": [
    "To invest in the company",
    "To help price and sell the shares",
    "To manage the company's finances",
    "To ensure the company's legal compliance"
  ],
  "answer": "To help price and sell the shares",
  "category": "IPO"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706691"
  },
  "question": "What is a common risk for investors during an IPO?",
  "options": [
    "The stock price can fall significantly after the offering",
    "The company may stop paying dividends immediately",
    "The company is required to distribute earnings",
    "The IPO process always guarantees a profit"
  ],
  "answer": "The stock price can fall significantly after the offering",
  "category": "IPO"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706692"
  },
  "question": "What is a stock?",
  "options": [
    "A type of bond",
    "A share of ownership in a company",
    "A government investment tool",
    "A loan issued to companies"
  ],
  "answer": "A share of ownership in a company",
  "category": "Basics Stock Markett"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706693"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is an example of a stock exchange?",
  "options": [
    "NASDAQ",
    "S&P 500",
    "Futures Market",
    "T-bill Market"
  ],
  "answer": "NASDAQ",
  "category": "Basics Stock Market"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706694"
  },
  "question": "What is a dividend?",
  "options": [
    "The price of a stock",
    "The interest paid on stocks",
    "A payment made to stockholders from company profits",
    "The cost of buying a stock"
  ],
  "answer": "A payment made to stockholders from company profits",
  "category": "Basics Stock Market"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706695"
  },
  "question": "What does it mean when a stock is said to be 'bullish'?",
  "options": [
    "The stock price is expected to decline",
    "The stock price is expected to rise",
    "The stock has high volatility",
    "The stock has a dividend yield"
  ],
  "answer": "The stock price is expected to rise",
  "category": "Basics Stock Market"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706696"
  },
  "question": "What does 'IPO' stand for in the stock market?",
  "options": [
    "Initial Private Offering",
    "International Public Offering",
    "Initial Public Offering",
    "Investor's Public Option"
  ],
  "answer": "Initial Public Offering",
  "category": "Stock Market Terms"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706697"
  },
  "question": "What is a 'bull market'?",
  "options": [
    "A market where prices are falling",
    "A market where prices are stable",
    "A market where prices are rising",
    "A market with low trading volume"
  ],
  "answer": "A market where prices are rising",
  "category": "Stock Market Terms"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706698"
  },
  "question": "What is a 'bear market'?",
  "options": [
    "A market where prices are rising",
    "A market where prices are falling",
    "A market with high investor sentiment",
    "A market driven by speculation"
  ],
  "answer": "A market where prices are falling",
  "category": "Stock Market Terms"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb9706699"
  },
  "question": "What does 'dividend yield' refer to?",
  "options": [
    "The growth rate of a stock",
    "The income generated from stock investment expressed as a percentage of the stock price",
    "The total value of dividends paid per year",
    "The total market capitalization of a company"
  ],
  "answer": "The income generated from stock investment expressed as a percentage of the stock price",
  "category": "Stock Market Terms"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970669a"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is the largest stock exchange in the world by market capitalization?",
  "options": [
    "London Stock Exchange",
    "NASDAQ",
    "Tokyo Stock Exchange",
    "New York Stock Exchange"
  ],
  "answer": "New York Stock Exchange",
  "category": "Global Stock Markets"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970669b"
  },
  "question": "Which country has the Tokyo Stock Exchange as its major stock exchange?",
  "options": [
    "China",
    "India",
    "Japan",
    "South Korea"
  ],
  "answer": "Japan",
  "category": "Global Stock Markets"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970669c"
  },
  "question": "Which global stock index represents the stock performance of the top 500 companies in the United States?",
  "options": [
    "DAX",
    "Nikkei 225",
    "S&P 500",
    "FTSE 100"
  ],
  "answer": "S&P 500",
  "category": "Global Stock Markets"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "67c7fc19cca1a4afb970669d"
  },
  "question": "What is the name of the stock exchange located in Hong Kong?",
  "options": [
    "Hong Kong Stock Exchange",
    "Shanghai Stock Exchange",
    "Shenzhen Stock Exchange",
    "Taiwan Stock Exchange"
  ],
  "answer": "Hong Kong Stock Exchange",
  "category": "Global Stock Markets"
}]